Sculpture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Italy (Box 52)
  - Modern (Box 56)
    - 20th century (Box 56)
      - Urbano Da Cortona (Box 96)
      - Valdambrino, Francesco, 14th-15th century (Box 96)
      - Vasari, Giorgio, 1511-1574 (Box 96)
      - Vecchietta, IL ca.1412-1480 (Box 96)
        - Various (Box 96)
        - Florence (Box 96)
        - Montemerano (Box 96)
        - New York (Box 96)
        - Rome (Box 96–97)
        - Siena (Box 97)
          - Various (Box 97)
          - Cathedral (Box 97)
      - Verrocchio, Andrea Del, 1435-1488 (Box 97)
        - Berlin (Box 97)
        - Detroit (Box 97)
        - Florence (Box 97)
          - Bargello (Box 97)
            - Various titles (Box 97)
            - David, 1470-1475 (Box 97)
            - Madonna & Child (Box 97)
          - Opera Del Duomo (Cathedral Museum) (Box 97)
          - Orsanmichele (Box 98)
          - Palazzo Pitti (Box 98)
          - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 98)
          - S. Lorenzo (Box 98)
            - Various (Box 98)
            - Medici Tomb (Box 98)
            - Marble Lavabo (Box 98)
          - S. Trinita (Box 98)
        - Paris (Box 98)
        - Pistoia (Box 98–99)
        - San Francisco (Box 99)
        - Venice (Box 99)
        - Washington (Box 99)
          - Alexandre the Great (Box 99)
          - Guiliano De'Medici (Box 99)
          - Lorenzo De'Medici (Box 99)
      - Vianni, Alberto, 1906- (Box 99)
      - Vittoria, Alessandro, 1525-1608 (Box 99)
      - Walter of Munich (Box 99)
      - Wildt, Adolfo (Box 99)
- Portugal (Box 99)
  - Various (Box 99)
  - Vierira, Jorge (Box 99)
- Rumania (Box 99)
  - Brancusi, Constantin, 1876-1957 (Box 99)
    - Various (Box 99)
    - Bird (Box 99)
    - Endless Column (Box 100)
    - Fish (Box 100)
    - Heads: Boy-Girl (Box 100)
    - Kiss (Box 100)
    - Leda (Box 100)
    - Maiastra (Box 100)
    - Mademoiselle Pogany (Box 100)
    - Miracle (Box 100)
    - New Born (Box 100)
    - Sleeping Muse (Box 100)
    - Torso (Box 100)
- Russia (Box 100)
  - Various (Box 100)
  - Androusov, Vadime (Box 100)
  - Archipenko, Alexander, 1887-. (Box 100)
  - Gabo, Naum, 1890- (Box 100)
    - Various Titles (Box 100)
    - New Haven (Box 100)
    - Rotterdam (Box 100)
  - Golubkina, A., 1864-1927 (Box 100)
  - Groubye, A. (Box 101)
  - Kozlovski, M.I., 1753-1802 (Box 101)
  - Malevich, Kasmir, 1878-1935 (Box 101)
  - Martos, I.P. (Box 101)
  - Mudunitsky, K.K., 1899-1936 (Box 101)
  - Meduniezky (Box 101)
  - Mendeleviche, I.A. (Box 101)
  - Merkourov, S. (Box 101)
  - Mukhina, Vera, 1889-1953 (Box 101)
  - Pevsner, Antoine, 1886-1962 (Box 101)
  - Rastrelli, C., 1675-1755 (Box 101)
  - Rodchenko, Alexandre, 1891-1956 (Box 101)
  - Shair, Ivan (Box 101)
  - Tatlin, Vladimir, E., 1885-1953 (Box 101)
  - Tchelitchew, Pavel (Box 101)
  - Yourievitch, Serge (Box 101)
  - Zadkine, Ossip, 1890- (Box 101)
- Spain (Box 101)
  - Romanesque (Box 101)
    - 11th century (Box 101)
    - 12th century (Box 101)
    - 13th century (Box 102)
  - Gothic (Box 102)
    - Tomb of S. Vincent & His Sisters (Box 102)
    - 14th century (Box 102)
    - 15th century (Box 102)
      - Various (Box 102)
      - Tomb of a Knight of Santiago (Box 102)
  - Renaissance (Box 102)
    - 16th century (Box 102)
    - 17th century (Box 102)
  - Known Artists (Box 102)
    - Arfe, Juan de (Box 102)
    - Balba, Jeronimo de, ac.1706-1750 (Box 102)
    - Becerra, Gaspar (Box 102)
    - Berruguette, Alonso, 1480-1561 (Box 102)
      - Faenza (Box 102–103)
      - Toledo (Box 103)
      - Valladolid (Box 103)
    - Cano, Alonso, 1601-1667 (Box 103)
    - Carmona, Luis Salvador, 1730-1807 (Box 103)
    - Chili, Manuel (Box 103)
    - Escaler, Lamberto (Box 103)
    - Fernandez, Gregorio, 1576-1636 (Box 103)
    - Forment, Damian, d.1541 (Box 103)
    - Gargallo, Pablo, 1881-19 (Box 103)
    - Gonzalez, Julio, 1876-1942 (Box 103)
    - El Greco (Box 103)
    - Gris, Juan, 1887-1927 (Box 103)
    - Hernandez, Gregorio (Box 103)
    - Juni, Juan de, ca.1507-1577 (Box 103)
    - Leoni, Pompeo, ca.1533-1608 (Box 103)
    - Mena, Pedro de, 1628-1688 (Box 103)
    - Mercadante, Lorenzo (Box 103)
    - Montañes, Juan Martinez, 1568-1649 (Box 103)
    - Ordoñez, Bartholomew, 1520 (Box 103)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 81-1973 (Box 104)
      - 1910-1919 (Box 104)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 104)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 104)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 104)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 104)
    - Siloe, Diego de, 1495-1563 (Box 104)
    - Siloe, Gil de (Box 104)
      - Various (Box 104)
      - Burgos (Box 104)
    - Tome, Narciso (Box 104)
    - Valenciennes, Juan de (Box 104)
    - Vallfogona, Pedro Juan (Box 104)
    - Velasquez, Cristobal (Box 104)
    - Vigarni, Felipe, 1470-1543 (Box 105)
    - Zarzillo, Francisco, 1707-1781 (Box 105)
    - Zoan, Pedro (Box 105)
- Sweden (Box 105)
  - Johnson, Ivar (Box 105)
  - Milles, Carl, 1875-1955 (Box 105)
    - Various (Box 105)
    - Monuments (Box 105)
    - Fountains (Box 105)
      - Various (Box 105)
      - Diana Fountain (Box 105)
      - Folke-Filbert Fountain (Box 105)
      - Orpheus Fountain (Box 105)
      - Poseidon Fountain (Box 105)
  - Sergel, Johan Tobias, 1740-1814 (Box 106)
- Switzerland (Box 106)
  - Various (Box 106)
  - Bill, Max, 1908- (Box 106)
  - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1965 (Box 106)
    - Various (Box 106)
    - New York (Box 106)
    - Paris (Box 106)
  - Oppenheim, Meret, 1913- (Box 106)
- Yugoslavia (Box 106)
  - Various Artists (Box 106)
  - Mestrovic, Ivan, 1883- (Box 106)
- Latin America (Box 106)
  - General (Box 106)
  - Argentina (Box 106)
  - Bolivia (Box 106)
  - Brazil (Box 106)
    - Various Artists (Box 106)
    - Lisboa, Antonio Francisco (Box 106–107)
  - Chile (Box 107)
  - Colombia (Box 107)
  - Ecuador (Box 107)
  - Mexico (Box 107)
    - 16th century (Box 107)
    - 17th century (Box 107)
    - 18th century (Box 107)
    - 19th - 20th century (Box 107)
      - Known Artists (Box 107)
        - Various (Box 107)
        - Tolsa, Manuel (Box 107)
  - Paraguay (Box 107)
  - Peru (Box 107)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 107)
- Canada (Box 107)
  - Archambault, Louis (Box 107)
- United States (Box 107)
  - Southwest (Box 107)
    - Artists Unknowns (Box 107)
  - 17th Century (Box 108)
    - Gravestones (Box 108)
  - 18th Century (Box 108)
    - Gravestones (Box 108)
      - Connecticut (Box 108)
      - Massachusetts (Box 108)
      - Rhode Island (Box 108)
  - 19th – 20th Century (Box 108)
    - Artists Unknown (Box 108–109)
    - Adams, Herbert (Box 109)
    - Aitkens, Robert (Box 109)
    - Allen, Frederick (Box 109)
    - Amateis, E. (Box 109)
    - Ames, Alexander (Box 109)
    - Amino, Leo (Box 109)
    - Angel, John (Box 109)
    - Aronson, Boris (Box 109)
    - Augur, Hezekiah (Box 109)
    - Hall, Thomas, 1819-1911 (Box 109)
    - Barnard, George Grey, 1863-1938 (Box 109)
    - Bartlett, Paul (Box 109)
    - Borglum, Gutzon (Box 109)
    - Borglum, Solon (Box 110)
    - Browere, John, 1792-1834 (Box 110)
    - Brown, Henry Kirk, 1814-1886 (Box 110)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1898- (Box 110)
      - Mobiles (Box 110)
      - Stabiles (Box 110)
      - Wire Constructions (Box 110)
    - Callery, Mary (Box 110)
    - Campoli, Cosmo, 1923- (Box 110)
    - Clark, Alan (Box 110)
    - Conrad, C. (Box 110)
    - Crawford, Thomas (Box 110)
    - Dallin, Cyrus E. (Box 110)
    - Davidson, Jo (Box 110)
    - Davis, Richard (Box 110)
    - De Rivera, Jose, 1904- (Box 110)
    - Dowler, Charles (Box 110)
    - Duveneck, Frank (Box 110)
    - Eakins, Thomas (Box 111)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1906- (Box 111)
    - Flannagan, John, 1895- (Box 111)
    - Follettt, Jean, 1917- (Box 111)
    - Foster, Robert (Box 111)
    - Frager, James Earle (Box 111)
    - French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1981 (Box 111)
      - Boston (Box 111)
      - Brooklyn (Box 111)
      - Cambridge (Box 111)
      - Chicago (Box 111)
      - Concord (Box 111)
      - New York (Box 111)
      - Washington (Box 111)
    - Greenough, Horatio, 1805-1852 (Box 111)
    - Greenough, Richard, 1819-1904 (Box 111)
    - Gregory, John, 1879- (Box 111)
    - Hancock, W. (Box 111)
    - Hare, Davis (Box 111)
    - Hayes, David, 1931- (Box 111)
    - Herms, George, 1935- (Box 112)
    - Hoffman, Malvina, 1897- (Box 112)
    - Hosmer, Harriet, 1830-1908 (Box 112)
    - Hughes, Ball, 1806-1868 (Box 112)
    - Ives, Chauncey B., 1810-1894 (Box 112)
    - Jennewein, Carl Paul, 1890- (Box 112)
    - Jones, Thomas Hudson (Box 112)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, 1882- (Box 112)
    - Lassaw, Thomas, 1912- (Box 112)
    - Lawrie, Lee (Box 112)
    - Lippold, Richard, 1915- (Box 112)
    - Lipton, Seymour, 1903- (Box 112)
    - McCartan, Edward, 1879- (Box 112)
    - McIntire, Samuel, 1757-1811 (Box 112)
    - McMonnies, Frederick, 1863- (Box 113)
    - McNeil, Hermon, Atkins, 1866- (Box 113)
    - Man, Ray, 1890- (Box 113)
      Xx Miscellaneous Movements- Dada & Surrealism
    - Manship, Paul, 1885- (Box 113)
      - Various (Box 113)
      - New York (Box 113)
    - Marisol (Box 113)
      Xx for Comparison see Sculpture Pre-Columbian Andean-General Peru, Human Figures of wood and cloth
    - Mead, Larkin Goldsmith (Box 113)
    - Mills, Clark, 1815-1883 (Box 113)
    - Milmore, Martin, 1844-1883 (Box 113)
    - Monroe, Keith (Box 113)
    - Morris, George (Box 113)
    - Morse, Samuel F.B., 1791-1872 (Box 113)
    - Mozier, Joseph, 1812-1870 (Box 113)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 1885-19 (Box 113)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1904- (Box 113)
    - Nivola, Constantino (Box 114)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, 1904- (Box 114)
    - O'Connor, Andrew, 1884- (Box 114)
    - Palmer, Erastus Dow, 1817-1904 (Box 114)
    - Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873 (Box 114)
    - Pratt, Bela Lyon, 1867-1917 (Box 114)
    - Putnam, Arthur, 1873- (Box 114)
    - Rhind, John M., 1860-1934 (Box 114)
    - Rimmer, William, 1816-1879 (Box 114)
    - Rinehart, William H., 1825-1874 (Box 114)
    - Rogers, John, 1829-1904 (Box 114)
    - Rogers, Randolph, 1825-1892 (Box 114)
    - Rosenthal, Bernard (Box 114)
    - Roszak, Theodore, 1907- (Box 114–115)
    - Rush, William, 1756-1833 (Box 115)
    - St. Gaudens, Augustus, 1848-1907 (Box 115)
      Xx for Portrait see U.S. Painting Cox, Kenyon
      - Various (Box 115)
      - Chicago (Box 115)
      - New Haven (Box 115)
      - New York (Box 115)
      - Paris (Box 115)
      - Philadelphia (Box 115)
      - Washington (Box 115)
    - Sargent, John D. (Box 115)
    - Schmidt, Julius, 1923- (Box 115)
    - Shrady, Henry, 1871-1922 (Box 115)
    - Smith, David, 1906- (Box 115)
    - Snowden, George (Box 115)
    - Stankiewicz, Richard, 1922- (Box 115)
    - Stone, Horatio, 1808-1875 (Box 115)
    - Storrs, John, 1885- (Box 115)
    - Stony, William, 1819-1895 (Box 115–116)
    - Tajiri (Box 116)
    - Taft, Lorado, 1860-1936 (Box 116)
    - Ward, John Q.A., 1830-1910 (Box 116)
    - Weinberg, Elbert, 1928- (Box 116)
    - Wright, Joseph, 1756-1793 (Box 116)
    - Wright, Patience (Box 116)
    - Yellin, Samuel (Box 116)
    - Young, Mahonri (Box 116)
    - Zorach, William (Box 116)